{"metadata":{"generator":"Captivate","generatorVersion":"10.0.1","schemaVersion":"","author":"author","title":"","description":"project description","email":"author@company.com","website":"www.company.com","tags":"","thumbnail":"","source":"assets","durationInFrames":6900,"frameRate":30,"totalSlides":11,"width":640,"height":480,"responsive":false,"scalable":false,"launchFile":"index.html"},"contentStructure":[{"id":"si1270","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":" ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si4377","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":" ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si4392","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":" ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Text_Caption_2","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_2","title":"Information Security Awareness Quiz Cyber Safety at Home ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"Text_Caption_3","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_3","title":"Take our Security Quiz to test your knowledge.   Click on Begin to start. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"SmartShape_2","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_2","title":"Begin ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si19016","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Begin ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si19034","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Begin ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Text_Caption_106","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_106","title":"Brought to you by the Information Security Branch  Office of the Chief Information Officer ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"Image_250","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Image_250","roles":{}},{"id":"Slide4365","class":"Normal Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["si1270","si4377","si4392","Text_Caption_2","Text_Caption_3","SmartShape_2","si19016","si19034","Text_Caption_106","Image_250"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":90},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide4365"}}},{"id":"Image_253","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Image_253","roles":{}},{"id":"si12441","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_338","roles":{}},{"id":"si12349","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_327","title":"1.\tWorking from home means that I can work at my own pace without close contact with supervision or colleagues.  ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si12382","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_332","title":"A) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si12386","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_333","title":"True ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si12382_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"179","roles":{"answer":{"title":"True\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si20585","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"B) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si20589","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"False ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si20585_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"False\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":10}}}},{"id":"si12435","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_337","roles":{}},{"id":"si12459","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_42","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide12483q0","for":"Slide12483q0"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si12473","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_43","title":"Back ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"back","question":"Slide12483q0","for":"Slide12483q0"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si19347","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":">> ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeNext","question":"Slide12483q0","for":"Slide12483q0"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si19361","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"<< ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeBack","question":"Slide12483q0","for":"Slide12483q0"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si19593","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide12483q0","for":"Slide12483q0"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si19606","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide12483q0","for":"Slide12483q0"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si19621","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Back ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"back","question":"Slide12483q0","for":"Slide12483q0"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si19634","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Back ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"back","question":"Slide12483q0","for":"Slide12483q0"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si19649","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":">> ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeNext","question":"Slide12483q0","for":"Slide12483q0"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si19662","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":">> ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeNext","question":"Slide12483q0","for":"Slide12483q0"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si19677","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"<< ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeBack","question":"Slide12483q0","for":"Slide12483q0"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si19690","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"<< ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeBack","question":"Slide12483q0","for":"Slide12483q0"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si12405","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_334","title":"Correct - Answer:  B  When working from home, it is important to collaborate with your colleagues, share your work and stay informed to avoid duplication. Your supervisor will need to stay in touch to offer guidance and relay information. Being aware of the current notifications, especially in these ever-changing and challenging times, will assist in keeping you safe and productive.  Press anwhere or click ‘y’ to continue. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si12417","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_335","title":"Incorrect - Answer: B When working from home, it is important to collaborate with your colleagues, share your work and stay informed to avoid duplication. Your supervisor will need to stay in touch to offer guidance and relay information. Being aware of the current notifications, especially in these ever-changing and challenging times, will assist in keeping you safe and productive.  Press anwhere or click ‘y’ to continue. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si12429","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_336","title":"You must answer the question before continuing. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide12483","class":"Question Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["si1270","Image_253","si12349","si12386","si20589","si12459","si12473","si19347","si19361","si19593","si19606","si19621","si19634","si19649","si19662","si19677","si19690","si12429"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":90},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide12483"},"question":{"interactionId":"12329","quizId":458,"title":"Multiple Choice","text":"1.\tWorking from home means that I can work at my own pace without close contact with supervision or colleagues.\r\r","ikc":false,"type":"graded","interactionType":"choice","ramdomized":false,"correctAnswers":["B"],"score":{"weight":10,"penalty":0}}}},{"id":"Image_258","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Image_258","roles":{}},{"id":"si31507","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_1053","roles":{}},{"id":"si31426","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_960","title":"2.\tWe are always told to back up our personal information regularly. When working from home, I do not need to be concerned about backing up my data.  ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si31437","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_1045","title":"A) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si31441","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_1046","title":"True ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si31437_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"179_505","roles":{"answer":{"title":"True\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si31448","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_1047","title":"B) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si31452","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_1048","title":"False ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si31448_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"506","roles":{"answer":{"title":"False\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":10}}}},{"id":"si31501","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_1052","roles":{}},{"id":"si31529","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_195","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide31696q1","for":"Slide31696q1"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si31547","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_196","title":"Back ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"back","question":"Slide31696q1","for":"Slide31696q1"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si31569","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_197","title":">> ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeNext","question":"Slide31696q1","for":"Slide31696q1"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si31587","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_198","title":"<< ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeBack","question":"Slide31696q1","for":"Slide31696q1"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si31599","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide31696q1","for":"Slide31696q1"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si31611","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide31696q1","for":"Slide31696q1"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si31623","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Back ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"back","question":"Slide31696q1","for":"Slide31696q1"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si31635","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Back ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"back","question":"Slide31696q1","for":"Slide31696q1"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si31647","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":">> ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeNext","question":"Slide31696q1","for":"Slide31696q1"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si31659","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":">> ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeNext","question":"Slide31696q1","for":"Slide31696q1"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si31671","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"<< ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeBack","question":"Slide31696q1","for":"Slide31696q1"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si31683","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"<< ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeBack","question":"Slide31696q1","for":"Slide31696q1"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si31471","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_1049","title":"Correct - Answer: B  Ensuring your data is backed up is one of the most important things you can do while working from home. If you are connected to your network, save your work regularly; your data centre will create backups as required. If you are working offline or independent of the network, ensure you log onto your network (even intermittently) and save your data on shared drives so the information is captured and backups created.  Press anwhere or click ‘y’ to continue. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si31483","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_1050","title":"Incorrect - Answer: B  Ensuring your data is backed up is one of the most important things you can do while working from home. If you are connected to your network, save your work regularly; your data centre will create backups as required. If you are working offline or independent of the network, ensure you log onto your network (even intermittently) and save your data on shared drives so the information is captured and backups created.  Press anwhere or click ‘y’ to continue. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si31495","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_1051","title":"You must answer the question before continuing. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide31696","class":"Question Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["si1270","Image_258","si31426","si31441","si31452","si31529","si31547","si31569","si31587","si31599","si31611","si31623","si31635","si31647","si31659","si31671","si31683","si31495"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":90},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide31696"},"question":{"interactionId":"31406","quizId":458,"title":"Multiple Choice","text":"2.\tWe are always told to back up our personal information regularly. When working from home, I do not need to be concerned about backing up my data.\r\r","ikc":false,"type":"graded","interactionType":"choice","ramdomized":false,"correctAnswers":["B"],"score":{"weight":10,"penalty":0}}}},{"id":"Image_259","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Image_259","roles":{}},{"id":"si31815","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_1062","roles":{}},{"id":"si31734","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_961","title":"3.\tI need to send large files that don’t fit in an email, what is the best method for sending?  ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si31745","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_1054","title":"A) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si31749","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_1055","title":"Dropbox ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si31745_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"179_507","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Dropbox\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si31756","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_1056","title":"B) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si31760","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_1057","title":"Google Drive ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si31756_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"506_508","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Google Drive\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si32012","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"C) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si32016","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Box.com ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si32012_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Box.com\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si32027","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"D) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si32031","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Approved Transfer Service ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si32027_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Approved Transfer Service\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":10}}}},{"id":"si31809","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_1061","roles":{}},{"id":"si31837","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_199","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide32004q2","for":"Slide32004q2"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si31855","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_200","title":"Back ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"back","question":"Slide32004q2","for":"Slide32004q2"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si31877","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_201","title":">> ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeNext","question":"Slide32004q2","for":"Slide32004q2"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si31895","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_202","title":"<< ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeBack","question":"Slide32004q2","for":"Slide32004q2"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si31907","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide32004q2","for":"Slide32004q2"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si31919","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide32004q2","for":"Slide32004q2"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si31931","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Back ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"back","question":"Slide32004q2","for":"Slide32004q2"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si31943","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Back ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"back","question":"Slide32004q2","for":"Slide32004q2"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si31955","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":">> ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeNext","question":"Slide32004q2","for":"Slide32004q2"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si31967","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":">> ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeNext","question":"Slide32004q2","for":"Slide32004q2"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si31979","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"<< ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeBack","question":"Slide32004q2","for":"Slide32004q2"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si31991","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"<< ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeBack","question":"Slide32004q2","for":"Slide32004q2"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si31779","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_1058","title":"Correct - Answer: D  You must ensure that your transfer service follows your organization’s security or privacy policies. Many of the well-known services transfer data through data centres outside of Canada, are easily intruded upon, used as phishing vehicles to collect login credentials and have known vulnerabilities (sql injection, DoS, memory corruption, etc.). Only use the File Transfer Service approved by your organization such as Secure File Transfer Service (SFTS) for Government employees.  Press anwhere or click ‘y’ to continue. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si31791","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_1059","title":"Incorrect - Answer: D  You must ensure that your transfer service follows your organization’s security or privacy policies. Many of the well-known services transfer data through data centres outside of Canada, are easily intruded upon, used as phishing vehicles to collect login credentials and have known vulnerabilities (sql injection, DoS, memory corruption, etc.). Only use the File Transfer Service approved by your organization such as Secure File Transfer Service (SFTS) for Government employees.  Press anwhere or click ‘y’ to continue. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si31803","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_1060","title":"You must answer the question before continuing. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide32004","class":"Question Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["si1270","Image_259","si31734","si31749","si31760","si32016","si32031","si31837","si31855","si31877","si31895","si31907","si31919","si31931","si31943","si31955","si31967","si31979","si31991","si31803"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":90},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide32004"},"question":{"interactionId":"31714","quizId":458,"title":"Multiple Choice","text":"3.\tI need to send large files that don’t fit in an email, what is the best method for sending?\r\r","ikc":false,"type":"graded","interactionType":"choice","ramdomized":false,"correctAnswers":["D"],"score":{"weight":10,"penalty":0}}}},{"id":"Image_260","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Image_260","roles":{}},{"id":"si32183","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_1075","roles":{}},{"id":"si32080","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_962","title":"4.\tSuppose you had an online meeting and following that meeting, you start seeing the topics you discussed on your Internet page. Your immediate reaction is?  ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si32091","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_1063","title":"A) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si32095","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_1064","title":"This is a coincidence, just ignore it ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si32091_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"179_509","roles":{"answer":{"title":"This is a coincidence, just ignore it\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si32102","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_1065","title":"B) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si32106","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_1066","title":"Someone has guessed your preferences and created an algorithm ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si32102_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"506_510","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Someone has guessed your preferences and created an algorithm\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si32113","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_1067","title":"C) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si32117","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_1068","title":"Someone is eavesdropping on your meeting ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si32113_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"511","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Someone is eavesdropping on your meeting\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":10}}}},{"id":"si32124","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_1069","title":"D) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si32128","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_1070","title":"Your organization is monitoring and sending updates to your computer ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si32124_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"512","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Your organization is monitoring and sending updates to your computer\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si32177","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_1074","roles":{}},{"id":"si32205","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_203","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide32372q3","for":"Slide32372q3"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si32223","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_204","title":"Back ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"back","question":"Slide32372q3","for":"Slide32372q3"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si32245","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_205","title":">> ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeNext","question":"Slide32372q3","for":"Slide32372q3"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si32263","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_206","title":"<< ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeBack","question":"Slide32372q3","for":"Slide32372q3"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si32275","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide32372q3","for":"Slide32372q3"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si32287","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide32372q3","for":"Slide32372q3"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si32299","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Back ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"back","question":"Slide32372q3","for":"Slide32372q3"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si32311","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Back ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"back","question":"Slide32372q3","for":"Slide32372q3"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si32323","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":">> ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeNext","question":"Slide32372q3","for":"Slide32372q3"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si32335","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":">> ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeNext","question":"Slide32372q3","for":"Slide32372q3"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si32347","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"<< ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeBack","question":"Slide32372q3","for":"Slide32372q3"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si32359","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"<< ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeBack","question":"Slide32372q3","for":"Slide32372q3"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si32147","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_1071","title":"Correct - Answer: C  Even with company-issued devices, it is still possible for others to intrude and eavesdrop on your meetings. Ensure you ‘harden’ your meetings: Make the meeting ‘Private’, carefully inspect the meeting link and invitees, allow only meeting organizers to perform tasks such as screen sharing and video, use a waiting room, pay close attention to who is actually attending the meeting and verify any ‘guests’.   Press anwhere or click ‘y’ to continue. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si32159","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_1072","title":"Incorrect - Answer: C  Even with company-issued devices, it is still possible for others to intrude and eavesdrop on your meetings. Ensure you ‘harden’ your meetings: Make the meeting ‘Private’, carefully inspect the meeting link and invitees, allow only meeting organizers to perform tasks such as screen sharing and video, use a waiting room, pay close attention to who is actually attending the meeting and verify any ‘guests’.  Press anwhere or click ‘y’ to continue. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si32171","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_1073","title":"You must answer the question before continuing. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide32372","class":"Question Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["si1270","Image_260","si32080","si32095","si32106","si32117","si32128","si32205","si32223","si32245","si32263","si32275","si32287","si32299","si32311","si32323","si32335","si32347","si32359","si32171"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":90},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide32372"},"question":{"interactionId":"32060","quizId":458,"title":"Multiple Choice","text":"4.\tSuppose you had an online meeting and following that meeting, you start seeing the topics you discussed on your Internet page. Your immediate reaction is?\r\r","ikc":false,"type":"graded","interactionType":"choice","ramdomized":false,"correctAnswers":["C"],"score":{"weight":10,"penalty":0}}}},{"id":"Image_261","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Image_261","roles":{}},{"id":"si32521","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_1088","roles":{}},{"id":"si32418","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_963","title":"5.\tWhat are some of the methods criminals use to interfere or collect information from your online meetings?    Choose all that apply:  ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si32429","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_1076","title":"A) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si32433","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_1077","title":"Bombing – interjecting inappropriate video or images ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si32433","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide32710q4"},"answer":{"title":"dummy title","index":-1,"score":{}}}},{"id":"si32429_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Bombing – interjecting inappropriate video or images\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si32440","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_1078","title":"B) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si32444","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_1079","title":"Snooping – secretly listening or watching, capturing information and images ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si32444","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide32710q4"},"answer":{"title":"dummy title","index":-1,"score":{}}}},{"id":"si32440_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Snooping – secretly listening or watching, capturing information and images\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si32451","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_1080","title":"C) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si32455","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_1081","title":"Hijacking – Taking over control of the meeting ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si32455","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide32710q4"},"answer":{"title":"dummy title","index":-1,"score":{}}}},{"id":"si32451_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Hijacking – Taking over control of the meeting\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":10}}}},{"id":"si32462","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_1082","title":"D) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si32466","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_1083","title":"Tapping – ‘Tap’ into your computer and take over your device ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si32466","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide32710q4"},"answer":{"title":"dummy title","index":-1,"score":{}}}},{"id":"si32462_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Tapping – ‘Tap’ into your computer and take over your device\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si32718","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"E) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si32722","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Hacking – stealing information of meeting attendees (Example: emails, uploaded documents, company positions and responses to polls) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si32722","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide32710q4"},"answer":{"title":"dummy title","index":-1,"score":{}}}},{"id":"si32718_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Hacking – stealing information of meeting attendees (Example: emails, uploaded documents, company positions and responses to polls)\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si32515","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_1087","roles":{}},{"id":"si32543","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_207","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide32710q4","for":"Slide32710q4"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si32561","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_208","title":"Back ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"back","question":"Slide32710q4","for":"Slide32710q4"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si32583","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_209","title":">> ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeNext","question":"Slide32710q4","for":"Slide32710q4"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si32601","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_210","title":"<< ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeBack","question":"Slide32710q4","for":"Slide32710q4"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si32613","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide32710q4","for":"Slide32710q4"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si32625","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide32710q4","for":"Slide32710q4"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si32637","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Back ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"back","question":"Slide32710q4","for":"Slide32710q4"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si32649","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Back ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"back","question":"Slide32710q4","for":"Slide32710q4"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si32661","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":">> ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeNext","question":"Slide32710q4","for":"Slide32710q4"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si32673","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":">> ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeNext","question":"Slide32710q4","for":"Slide32710q4"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si32685","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"<< ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeBack","question":"Slide32710q4","for":"Slide32710q4"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si32697","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"<< ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeBack","question":"Slide32710q4","for":"Slide32710q4"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si32485","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_1084","title":"Correct - Answer: A, B, C, E  Nearly all Web Conferencing tools (Example: ZOOM, Slack, WebEx, GoToMeeting and Google Hangouts) are vulnerable to hacking. Use only approved collaboration or web conferencing tools and follow your organization’s guidelines for their use.   Press anwhere or click ‘y’ to continue. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si32497","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_1085","title":"Incorrect - Answer: A, B, C, E  Nearly all Web Conferencing tools (Example: ZOOM, Slack, WebEx, GoToMeeting and Google Hangouts) are vulnerable to hacking. Use only approved collaboration or web conferencing tools and follow your organization’s guidelines for their use.  Press anwhere or click ‘y’ to continue. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si32509","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_1086","title":"You must answer the question before continuing. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide32710","class":"Question Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["si1270","Image_261","si32418","si32433","si32444","si32455","si32466","si32722","si32543","si32561","si32583","si32601","si32613","si32625","si32637","si32649","si32661","si32673","si32685","si32697","si32509"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":90},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide32710"},"question":{"interactionId":"32398","quizId":458,"title":"Multiple Choice","text":"5.\tWhat are some of the methods criminals use to interfere or collect information from your online meetings?    Choose all that apply:\r\r","ikc":false,"type":"graded","interactionType":"choice","ramdomized":false,"correctAnswers":["A","B","C","E"],"score":{"weight":10,"penalty":0}}}},{"id":"Image_262","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Image_262","roles":{}},{"id":"si32874","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_1101","roles":{}},{"id":"si32771","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_964","title":"6.\tYou are happily working on your computer and you suddenly receive an alert that your data has been encrypted and you must pay a ransom to gat it back. What is the first thing you should do?  ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si32782","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_1089","title":"A) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si32786","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_1090","title":"Turn off your computer ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si32782_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"179_517","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Turn off your computer\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si32793","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_1091","title":"B) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si32797","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_1092","title":"Disconnect from the network ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si32793_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"506_518","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Disconnect from the network\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":10}}}},{"id":"si32804","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_1093","title":"C) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si32808","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_1094","title":"Re-start your computer, it will disappear ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si32804_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"511_519","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Re-start your computer, it will disappear\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si32815","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_1095","title":"D) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si32819","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_1096","title":"Report it to your IT service desk ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si32815_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"512_520","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Report it to your IT service desk\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si32868","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_1100","roles":{}},{"id":"si32896","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_211","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide33063q5","for":"Slide33063q5"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si32914","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_212","title":"Back ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"back","question":"Slide33063q5","for":"Slide33063q5"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si32936","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_213","title":">> ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeNext","question":"Slide33063q5","for":"Slide33063q5"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si32954","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_214","title":"<< ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeBack","question":"Slide33063q5","for":"Slide33063q5"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si32966","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide33063q5","for":"Slide33063q5"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si32978","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide33063q5","for":"Slide33063q5"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si32990","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Back ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"back","question":"Slide33063q5","for":"Slide33063q5"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si33002","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Back ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"back","question":"Slide33063q5","for":"Slide33063q5"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si33014","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":">> ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeNext","question":"Slide33063q5","for":"Slide33063q5"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si33026","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":">> ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeNext","question":"Slide33063q5","for":"Slide33063q5"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si33038","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"<< ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeBack","question":"Slide33063q5","for":"Slide33063q5"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si33050","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"<< ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeBack","question":"Slide33063q5","for":"Slide33063q5"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si32838","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_1097","title":"Correct - Answer: B   If you turn off your computer, you limit the spread of the infection, but you have destroyed all forensic information to trace back to the intruder. Re-starting your computer will not remove the infection and will most likely spread it to others. You should definitely contact your IT service desk and report it but only after you have disconnected from the network to prevent it from infecting others.   Press anwhere or click ‘y’ to continue. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si32850","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_1098","title":"Incorrect - Answer: B   If you turn off your computer, you limit the spread of the infection, but you have destroyed all forensic information to trace back to the intruder. Re-starting your computer will not remove the infection and will most likely spread it to others. You should definitely contact your IT service desk and report it but only after you have disconnected from the network to prevent it from infecting others.  Press anwhere or click ‘y’ to continue. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si32862","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_1099","title":"You must answer the question before continuing. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide33063","class":"Question Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["si1270","Image_262","si32771","si32786","si32797","si32808","si32819","si32896","si32914","si32936","si32954","si32966","si32978","si32990","si33002","si33014","si33026","si33038","si33050","si32862"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":90},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide33063"},"question":{"interactionId":"32751","quizId":458,"title":"Multiple Choice","text":"6.\tYou are happily working on your computer and you suddenly receive an alert that your data has been encrypted and you must pay a ransom to gat it back. What is the first thing you should do?\r\r","ikc":false,"type":"graded","interactionType":"choice","ramdomized":false,"correctAnswers":["B"],"score":{"weight":10,"penalty":0}}}},{"id":"Image_263","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Image_263","roles":{}},{"id":"si33227","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_1114","roles":{}},{"id":"si33124","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_965","title":"7.\tWhat is the best defense against Ransomware?  ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si33135","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_1102","title":"A) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si33139","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_1103","title":"Back up your information ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si33135_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"179_521","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Back up your information\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":10}}}},{"id":"si33146","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_1104","title":"B) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si33150","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_1105","title":"Use strong, unique passwords ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si33146_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"506_522","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Use strong, unique passwords\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si33157","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_1106","title":"C) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si33161","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_1107","title":"Don’t click on unverified links or open unverified attachments ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si33157_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"511_523","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Don’t click on unverified links or open unverified attachments\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si33168","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_1108","title":"D) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si33172","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_1109","title":"Don’t visit unsecured websites (http://) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si33168_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"512_524","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Don’t visit unsecured websites (http://)\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si33221","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_1113","roles":{}},{"id":"si33249","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_215","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide33416q6","for":"Slide33416q6"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si33267","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_216","title":"Back ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"back","question":"Slide33416q6","for":"Slide33416q6"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si33289","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_217","title":">> ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeNext","question":"Slide33416q6","for":"Slide33416q6"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si33307","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_218","title":"<< ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeBack","question":"Slide33416q6","for":"Slide33416q6"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si33319","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide33416q6","for":"Slide33416q6"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si33331","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide33416q6","for":"Slide33416q6"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si33343","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Back ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"back","question":"Slide33416q6","for":"Slide33416q6"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si33355","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Back ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"back","question":"Slide33416q6","for":"Slide33416q6"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si33367","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":">> ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeNext","question":"Slide33416q6","for":"Slide33416q6"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si33379","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":">> ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeNext","question":"Slide33416q6","for":"Slide33416q6"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si33391","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"<< ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeBack","question":"Slide33416q6","for":"Slide33416q6"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si33403","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"<< ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeBack","question":"Slide33416q6","for":"Slide33416q6"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si33191","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_1110","title":"Correct - Answer: A  All of the above measures are best practices, however, if you can recall your backed-up information, you do not need to pay a ransom to get it back. It is important to remember that this does not protect you from the criminal selling your information (as in extortionware). To keep your information safe, you should engage in best practices to ensure no one can gain access to and steal your information in the first place.  Press anwhere or click ‘y’ to continue. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si33203","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_1111","title":"Incorrect - Answer: A  All of the above measures are best practices, however, if you can recall your backed-up information, you do not need to pay a ransom to get it back. It is important to remember that this does not protect you from the criminal selling your information (as in extortionware). To keep your information safe, you should engage in best practices to ensure no one can gain access to and steal your information in the first place.  Press anwhere or click ‘y’ to continue. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si33215","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_1112","title":"You must answer the question before continuing. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide33416","class":"Question Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["si1270","Image_263","si33124","si33139","si33150","si33161","si33172","si33249","si33267","si33289","si33307","si33319","si33331","si33343","si33355","si33367","si33379","si33391","si33403","si33215"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":90},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide33416"},"question":{"interactionId":"33104","quizId":458,"title":"Multiple Choice","text":"7.\tWhat is the best defense against Ransomware?\r\r","ikc":false,"type":"graded","interactionType":"choice","ramdomized":false,"correctAnswers":["A"],"score":{"weight":10,"penalty":0}}}},{"id":"Image_264","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Image_264","roles":{}},{"id":"si33565","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_1127","roles":{}},{"id":"si33462","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_966","title":"8.\tWhat is the best way to maintain your privacy and security while working from home?  ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si33473","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_1115","title":"A) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si33477","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_1116","title":"Face your monitors away from open windows or where others can view themc ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si33473_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"179_525","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Face your monitors away from open windows or where others can view themc\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si33484","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_1117","title":"B) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si33488","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_1118","title":"Put away your documents when you are done for the day (clean desk) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si33484_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"506_526","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Put away your documents when you are done for the day (clean desk)\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si33495","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_1119","title":"C) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si33499","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_1120","title":"Lock your computer when you leave it (Windows key + ‘L’) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si33495_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"511_527","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Lock your computer when you leave it (Windows key + ‘L’)\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si33506","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_1121","title":"D) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si33510","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_1122","title":"Know if anyone is piggybacking your Wi-Fi (Wireless watchers or IP scanning tools) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si33506_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"512_528","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Know if anyone is piggybacking your Wi-Fi (Wireless watchers or IP scanning tools)\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si33762","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"E) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si33766","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"All of the above ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si33762_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"All of the above\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":10}}}},{"id":"si33559","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_1126","roles":{}},{"id":"si33587","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_219","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide33754q7","for":"Slide33754q7"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si33605","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_220","title":"Back ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"back","question":"Slide33754q7","for":"Slide33754q7"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si33627","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_221","title":">> ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeNext","question":"Slide33754q7","for":"Slide33754q7"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si33645","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_222","title":"<< ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeBack","question":"Slide33754q7","for":"Slide33754q7"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si33657","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide33754q7","for":"Slide33754q7"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si33669","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide33754q7","for":"Slide33754q7"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si33681","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Back ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"back","question":"Slide33754q7","for":"Slide33754q7"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si33693","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Back ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"back","question":"Slide33754q7","for":"Slide33754q7"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si33705","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":">> ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeNext","question":"Slide33754q7","for":"Slide33754q7"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si33717","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":">> ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeNext","question":"Slide33754q7","for":"Slide33754q7"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si33729","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"<< ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeBack","question":"Slide33754q7","for":"Slide33754q7"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si33741","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"<< ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeBack","question":"Slide33754q7","for":"Slide33754q7"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si33529","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_1123","title":"Correct - Answer: E  52% of organizations believe that employees are the greatest threat to their information. When working from home, we are naturally more relaxed than at work. Ensure you maintain the same rigor with your habits and practices as if you were in the office (your information is just as valuable regardless of where you access it from).   Press anwhere or click ‘y’ to continue. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si33541","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_1124","title":"Incorrect - Answer:E  52% of organizations believe that employees are the greatest threat to their information. When working from home, we are naturally more relaxed than at work. Ensure you maintain the same rigor with your habits and practices as if you were in the office (your information is just as valuable regardless of where you access it from).   Press anwhere or click ‘y’ to continue. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si33553","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_1125","title":"You must answer the question before continuing. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide33754","class":"Question Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["si1270","Image_264","si33462","si33477","si33488","si33499","si33510","si33766","si33587","si33605","si33627","si33645","si33657","si33669","si33681","si33693","si33705","si33717","si33729","si33741","si33553"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":90},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide33754"},"question":{"interactionId":"33442","quizId":458,"title":"Multiple Choice","text":"8.\tWhat is the best way to maintain your privacy and security while working from home?\r\r","ikc":false,"type":"graded","interactionType":"choice","ramdomized":false,"correctAnswers":["E"],"score":{"weight":10,"penalty":0}}}},{"id":"Image_257","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Image_257","roles":{}},{"id":"Text_Caption_107","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_107","title":"Quiz Results ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"Image_256","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Image_256","roles":{}},{"id":"si6059","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{}},{"id":"si6083","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{}},{"id":"si6091","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{}},{"id":"si6055","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"You Scored: ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si6079","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Total Questions: ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si6087","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Accuracy: ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si6103","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{}},{"id":"si6107","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Continue ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"continue","question":"","for":""},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si6121","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Review Quiz ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"review","question":"","for":""},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si20489","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Continue ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"continue","question":"","for":""},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si20502","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Continue ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"continue","question":"","for":""},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si20517","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Review Quiz ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"review","question":"","for":""},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si20530","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Review Quiz ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"review","question":"","for":""},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide6038","class":"Question Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":[],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":90},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide6038"}}},{"id":"si6231","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":" ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Button_4","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_4","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"}}},{"id":"si19054","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"}}},{"id":"si19068","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"}}},{"id":"Text_Caption_5","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_5","title":"Thank you for taking the quiz.  To exit the quiz, close the browser window. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"SmartShape_9","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_9","title":"  Stay Current With   Information Security   By Subscribing to the    Weekly Security News Digest ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide6219","class":"Normal Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["si1270","si6231","Button_4","si19054","si19068","Text_Caption_5","SmartShape_9"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":6000},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide6219"}}},{"id":"Pool502","class":"pool","roles":{"pool":{"id":502,"name":"Pool1","questions":[]}}},{"id":"May2020Quiz","class":"project","title":"May2020Quiz","children":["Slide4365","Slide12483","Slide31696","Slide32004","Slide32372","Slide32710","Slide33063","Slide33416","Slide33754","Slide6038","Slide6219"],"roles":{"quiz":{"id":458,"branched":false,"submitAll":false,"review":true,"questions":["Slide12483q0","Slide31696q1","Slide32004q2","Slide32372q3","Slide32710q4","Slide33063q5","Slide33416q6","Slide33754q7"],"minScore":0,"maxScore":80,"passScore":64}}}],"contentSettings":{"global":{"branchAware":false},"toc":{"enabled":false},"playbar":{"enabled":true,"cc":false,"playPause":true,"back":true,"forward":true,"rewind":true,"close":true,"mute":true,"progressBar":true}},"contentReporting":{"CCCriteria":"quiz","CCData":{"quizData":"quiz_passed"},"SCCriteria":"quiz","SCData":{"quizData":"quiz_passed"},"exitNormalIfCompleted":false},"toc":[{"id":"Slide4365","title":"Slide 1"},{"id":"Slide12483","title":"Slide 2"},{"id":"Slide31696","title":"Slide 3"},{"id":"Slide32004","title":"Slide 4"},{"id":"Slide32372","title":"Slide 5"},{"id":"Slide32710","title":"Slide 6"},{"id":"Slide33063","title":"Slide 7"},{"id":"Slide33416","title":"Slide 8"},{"id":"Slide33754","title":"Slide 9"},{"id":"Slide6038","title":"Slide 10"},{"id":"Slide6219","title":"Slide 11"}]}